Today I have received some lovely crockery items from Vajas Collection
and I will
show them to you.  I have received crystal glasses.
First of all, I have
this glass set and it has four glasses and here are the
four and these are beautiful glasses.
I haven't found such glasses anywhere yet.   I
remember seeing one like this on the machine.
He sent me these three wooden trays.
Its quality is very good.  The design
is very cute.  Low Quality Its
quality is very good.  So these three
trays he sent me.  Lastly,
I have this cookware set.  There
are five pots in it.  Let me show you its quality.
Mostly I read that you should cook
food in steel utensils.  Do
not make it in non-stick.  This is what it looks like
and it's so cute.  It won't even spoil.  The
steel is very good and it
also has ml written on it to show how many ml it contains.  There
is a set of five leaves.  So you guys should
also go there, they have many lovely things.
You guys can also order